Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 7: Center Theatre Group files, 1732-2010
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotape, 1969-1991 (Box 1,738, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains thirteen 1/4 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: 1491, Tristesse, Sarafina!, Older and Wiper, Memorial Service Eleanor Pinkham, and Boat Pipes.
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotape, 1969-1991 (Box 1,739, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains eleven 1/4 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: The Vortex, Love Match Review, Sarafina!, Gregory Peck, Royal Shakespeare Company, Turnley Walker Critic at Large with Joel A. Spivak, Dr. Faustus, and Rosencrantz and Guildenstern.
  - Center Theatre Group 1 inch audiotapes, 1990-1991 (Box 1,740, Folder 1-5)
    This box contains five 1 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: Sarafina!, Cocktail Hour, Gossip, and Songs in your Head.
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotapes, 1990-1991 (Box 1,741, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains four 1/4 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: Sarafina! and The Vortex.
  - Center Theatre Group 1/4 inch audiotapes, 1990-1991 (Box 1,742, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains four 1/4 inch audiotapes and includes the following titles: Sarafina!, SFX, Songs in your Head, Contagious, and The Vortex.
  - Center Theatre Group vinyl records, 1973-1981 (Box 1,743, Folder 1-29)
    This box contains twenty-nine vinyl records and includes the following titles: A Streetcar Named Desire, The Crucible, The Prisoner of 2nd Avenue, Saint Joan, Midsummer Night's Dream, and Tintypes The New Musical.
  - Center Theatre Group audiocassettes, 1966-1997 (Box 1,744, Folder 1-30)
    This box contains thirty audiocassettes and includes the following titles: Mary Stuart, Candide, Kiev, Skipper Awards, Struck Dumb, The War in Heaven, On Golden Pond, Zenda, Another Part of the Forest, Conversations with Bernheimer: Ernest Fleischman, Conversations with Bernheimer: Gordon Davidson, The Hasty Heart, Conversations with Bernheimer: Heston-Fryer, Jack Weston feature, Neil Simon feature, Cleve Hermann on Liz Taylor and The Little Foxes, Hank Grant on-air spot, Hungry Tiger contest, Busker Alley, Bring On 'Da Noise, Bring On 'Da Funk, and Holiday.
  - Kenn Randall early LA theater survey, bound holograph book, and prompt books, 1902-1954 (Box 1,745, Folder 1-10)
  - Kenn Randall prompt books, 1930-1968 (Box 1,746, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains Annie Get Your Gun to The Desperate Hours.
  - Kenn Randall prompt books, 1930-1970 (Box 1,747, Folder 1-18)
    This box contains The Devil Also Dreams to The Little Accident.
  - Kenn Randall prompt books, 1930-1962 (Box 1,748, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains The Little Hat to Pegora.
  - Kenn Randall prompt books, 1929-1950 (Box 1,749, Folder 1-17)
    This box contains Peter Ibbetson to The Taming of the Shrew.
  - Kenn Randall prompt books and Theatre Arts Monthly, 1931-1954 (Box 1,750, Folder 1-11)
  - Kenn Randall theatre programs. A-K, undated (Box 1,751, Folder 1)
  - Kenn Randall theatre programs. L-Z, undated (Box 1,752, Folder 1)
  - Kenn Randall photographs, circa 1924-1966 (Box 1753, Folder 1-100)
    This box contains photographs of actors, choreographers, and conductors and includes 11 folders of images inscribed to William A. Clark, Jr.
  - Kenn Randall oversize photographs, 1938-1962 (Box 1754, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains oversize photographs of the following productions: Song of Norway, Yellow Jacket, and The King and I. This box also contains Theatre Arts, Stage, and Show publications.
  - Kenn Randall oversize photographs, A-M, undated (Box 1755, Folder 1-100)
  - Kenn Randall oversize photographs, N-W, undated (Box 1756, Folder 1-100)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre history index cards, A-H, 1893-1940 (Box 1757, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre history index cards, I-R, 1893-1940 (Box 1758, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre history index cards, S-Z, 1893-1940 (Box 1759, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes New York Legit, 1890-1925 (Box 1760, Folder 1-8)
    This box also contains theatre gross books dated 1920-1937.
  - Raymond F. Barnes New York Legit, 1925-1935 (Box 1761, Folder 1-6)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA, NY, and Chicago Legit records, 1925-1959 (Box 1762, Folder 1-7)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre performance records, 1910-1945 (Box 1763, Folder 1-7)
  - Raymond F. Barnes NY, LA, and Chicago Legit records, 1910-1950 (Box 1764, Folder 1-8)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA vaudeville and legit records, 1814-1949 (Box 1765, Folder 1-7)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA theatre programs, A-D, 1911-1969 (Box 1766, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA theatre programs, E-F, 1911-1969 (Box 1767, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA theatre programs, H-L, 1911-1969 (Box 1768, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA theatre programs, L-O, 1911-1969 (Box 1769, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes LA theatre programs, P-W, 1911-1969 (Box 1770, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Biltmore Theatre programs, 1925-1939 (Box 1771, Folder 1-2)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Biltmore Theatre programs, 1940-1949 (Box 1772, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Theatre programs, 1950-1964 (Box 1773, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Pasadena Playhouse programs, 1925-1933 (Box 1774, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Pasadena Playhouse programs, 1934-1967 (Box 1775, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Shrine Auditorium programs, 1927-1930 (Box 1776, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Shrine Auditorium programs, 1931-1949 (Box 1777, Folder 1-27)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Shrine Auditorium programs, 1950-1979 (Box 1778, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Greek Theatre programs and reviews, 1935-1969 (Box 1779, Folder 1)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Greek Theatre programs and reviews, 1970-1979 (Box 1780, Folder 1-10)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, A-B, circa 1956-1976 (Box 1781, Folder 1-34)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, C-F, circa 1955-1985 (Box 1782, Folder 1-38)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, G-L, 1955-1985 (Box 1783, Folder 1-41)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, M-R, 1955-1985 (Box 1784, Folder 1-37)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, R-U, 1955-1985 (Box 1785, Folder 1-39)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Huntington Hartford Theatre programs and reviews, V-Y, 1955-1985 (Box 1786, Folder 1-13)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Shubert Theater programs and reviews, 1972-1985 (Box 1787, Folder 1-29)
  - Raymond F. Barnes Pantages Theater programs and reviews, 1977-2000 (Box 1788, Folder Unknown)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre playbill and program scrapbooks, circa late 1800s - early 1900s (Box 1789, Folder 1-4)
    This box also contains one Fred Harvey restaurant menu and three photographs, including Elisabeth Rethberg and Lynden Behymer.
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre playbill scrapbooks, 1881-1888 (Box 1790, Folder 1-2)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre playbill scrapbooks, 1889-1904 (Box 1791, Folder 1-2)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre programs, 1901-1904 (Box 1792, Folder 1-5)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre programs, 1904-1915 (Box 1793, Folder 1-7)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre programs, 1911-1927 (Box 1794, Folder 1-8)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre programs, 1930s (Box 1795, Folder 1-5)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre programs, 1940s (Box 1796, Folder 1-6)
  - Raymond F. Barnes photographs, 1910-1982 (Box 1797)
    This box also contains Barnes' autograph book, Olga Rosenthal correspondence, Chicago theatre critic O.L. "Doc" Hall correspondence, and autographed photographs collected by Kenn Randall.
  - Raymond F. Barnes photographs, undated (Box 1798, Folder 1-39)
  - Raymond F. Barnes theatre posters, undated (Box 1799, Folder 1-18)
  - George Zoritch Playbill magazines, 1939-1971 (Box 1800, Folder 1-11)
  - George Zoritch photographs, correspondence, and programs, 1921-1977 (Box 1801, Folder 1-7)
  - George Zoritch photographs, posters, and programs, 1939-1976 (Box 1802, Folder 1-24)
  - Olga Rosenthal correspondence and New York City Opera photographs, 1945-1978 (Box 1803, Folder 1-8)
    This box also contains a Shubert Theatre Playbill dated 1945.
  - Leiland A. Irish Overture magazines, 1952-1956 (Box 1804, Folder 1-100)
  - Leiland A. Irish High Fidelity magazines, 1965-1967 (Box 1805, Folder 1-5)
  - Leiland A. Irish sheet music and LA theatre history data, 1889-1910 (Box 1806, Folder 1-7)
  - Charles Coburn drama publications, 1893-1948 (Box 1807, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains an index of all publications contained in boxes 1,807 to 1,809.
  - Charles Coburn drama publications, 1893-1948 (Box 1808, Folder 1-22)
  - Charles Coburn drama publications, 1893-1948 (Box 1809, Folder 1-14)
  - Charles Coburn sheet music, 1884-1910 (Box 1810, Folder 1-17)
    This box contains Schirmer's Library volumes and Gilbert & Sullivan opera scores.
  - Charles Coburn sheet music, 1899-1916 (Box 1811, Folder 1-10)
    This box also contains a list of music in boxes 1811, 1812 and 1813.
  - Charles Coburn sheet music, 1896-1935 (Box 1812, Folder 1-13)
  - Charles Coburn sheet music, 1890-1914 (Box 1813, Folder 1-3)
  - Music manuscripts, 1732-1886 (Box 1814, Folder 1-3)
    This box contains a Sonata for the Piano Forte by Valentino Niccolai published circa 1790, Dr. Haydn's VI original Canzonettas, for the Voice with an Accompaniment, for the Piano-Forte printed for and inscribed by Haydn, and a holograph manuscript signed F. Liszt of a symphonic poem, "Ce qu'on entend sur la montagne"(Symphonische Dichtung [Nr. 1]) circa 1850s.
- Series 8: Fundraising organization files, 1962-2015
  On June 26, 1968, Music Center founder, Dorothy Buffum Chandler, convened an afternoon reception of 27 women in Los Angeles at the home of Virginia Ramo. After tea, sandwiches, and cakes, Chandler announced that she was organizing the Blue Ribbon 400: Blue Ribbon because she liked the name she had given to a committee of women to raise the final $1 million of private funding needed to build the Music Center complex in 1963; and 400 because once the membership reached that number, it would be closed. Blue Ribbon members paid dues, planned, and sponsored the Music Center's social, educational, and cultural activities.
  Blue Ribbon member financial contributions would go to what is now the annual Music Center Unified Fund campaign, which provides support for all the Music Center resident companies: The Los Angeles Philharmonic, Center Theatre Group, Joffrey Ballet, the Los Angeles Music Center Opera, and the Los Angeles Master Chorale.
  Founded in 1976, Club 100 includes more than 100 women who support the performing arts through education, advocacy, and fundraising. The purpose of Club 100 is to train its members and other Music Center volunteer groups to be effective fundraisers for the Music Center Unified Fund and leading volunteers for the Music Center. Club 100's membership contributes more than $500,000 annually to the Center and sponsors the Distinguished Artist Award to honor members of the artistic community.
  Founded in 1978 by Thornton Bradshaw, Charles T. Manatt, and other Music Center supporters, the Fraternity of Friends is a group of businessmen and entertainment industry executives who share a common interest in the performing arts and believe that the well-being of the Center is directly linked to the betterment of Los Angeles. The Fraternity of Friends' combined membership contributes more than $500,000 annually to the Center.
  LA Alive! is an annual, free, two-day arts festival that celebrates the ethnic diversity of Los Angeles.
  Sources: "The Blue Ribbon Story" researched and written by Betty Goodwin, Box 1,815, Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles. By-Laws of Club 100, Box 1825, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles. "Fraternity of Friends" informational sheet, Box 1850, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles. The Music Center Fact Sheet, August 1, 1990. "Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles County", Box 402, Folder 8, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
  The Fundraising organization files range in date from 1962-2015 and contain Blue Ribbon invitations, correspondence, press, instruction guides, and rosters; Blue Ribbon Children's Festival photographs, flyers, programs, invitations, publicity, education guides, audio, and audiovisual materials; Club 100 scrapbooks, photographs, rosters, brochures, clippings, notebook, photograph albums, and digital materials; Distinguished Artist Award binders, programs, and audiovisual materials; Music Center Unified Fund Annual Reports, press files, campaign files, donor photographs, samples book, binders, ephemera, and memorabilia; Mercado press files and memorabilia; Music Center Fundraising book paste-ups; Fraternity of Friends photograph albums, rosters, invitations, newsletters, and scrapbook; LA Alive! photographs, gala files, programs, publicity, slides, digital, and audiovisual materials; Family Festival photographs; and A Community of Angels project files.
  - Blue Ribbon invitations, correspondence, and press, 1962-2002 (Box 1,815, Folder 1-15)
  - Blue Ribbon clippings, instruction guides, and rosters, 1968-2005 (Box 1,816, Folder 1-11)
  - Blue Ribbon Children's Festival photographs, flyers, and programs, 1978-1995 (Box 1,817, Folder 1-9)
    Folder 5 contains one CD of 2004 Children's Festival photographs. Folder 6 contains four CDs of Children's Festival photographs dated 2006-2008.
  - Blue Ribbon Children's Festival publicity and education guides, 1998-2008 (Box 1,818, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains six audiocassettes, three DVDs, and two CDs.
  - A Journey Through the Music Center books, 2004-2015 (Box 1,819, Folder 1-10)
  - Blue Ribbon Children's Festival programs and invitations, 1970-2004 (Box 1,820, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains five VHSs, three audiocassettes, and one MiniDV.
  - Blue Ribbon Children's Festival audiovisual materials, 1980-2000 (Box 1,821, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains eight VHSs, a 1 inch videotape, and one audiocassette.
  - Blue Ribbon Children's Festival U-Matics and VHSs, 1989-1994 (Box 1,822, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains two U-Matics and eight VHSs.
  - Blue Ribbon Holiday and Children's Festival audiovisual materials, 1989-2005 (Box 1,823, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains eight audiocassettes, six VHSs, and one Blue Ribbon 25th Anniversary Tribute DVD.
  - Club 100 photographs, 1979-1992 (Box 1,824, Folder 1-35)
  - Club 100 rosters, brochures, and clippings, 1979-2007 (Box 1,825, Folder 1-8)
  - Club 100 scrapbook and photographs, 1982-2009 (Box 1,826, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains seven CDs of Distinguished Artist Awards photographs.
  - Club 100 rosters, photographs, and binder, 1982-2001 (Box 1,827, Folder 1-4)
  - Distinguished Artist Award programs and binder, 1990-1998 (Box 1,828, Folder 1-10)
  - Club 100 scrapbook and photographs, 1975-1980 (Box 1,829, Folder 1)
  - Club 100 photograph album, 1993 (Box 1,830, Folder 1)
  - Club 100 photographs, 1993-1996 (Box 1,831, Folder 1-10)
  - Club 100 photograph album, 1996-1998 (Box 1,832, Folder 1)
  - Club 100 photograph albums, 1999-2004 (Box 1,833, Folder 1-6)
  - Club 100 photographs and Distinguished Artist Award binder, 2001-2007 (Box 1,834, Folder Unknown)
    This box contains three CDs of 30th Anniversary Membership Tea photographs.
  - Distinguished Artist Award Betacams, 1998, 2001 (Box 1,835, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains four Betacams.
  - Distinguished Artist Award and Club 100 Membership audiovisual materials, 1997-2001 (Box 1,836, Folder 1-14)
    This box contains thirteen VHSs and one Betacam.
  - Distinguished Artists Award VHSs, 1997-2003 (Box 1,837, Folder 1-15)
    This box contains fifteen VHSs.
  - Club 100 digital and audiovisual materials, 1997, 2007 (Box 1,838, Folder 1-16)
    This box contains two Distinguished Artist Award U-Matics, three Distinguished Artist Award Betacams, and eleven CDs of Club 100 Installation Tea photographs.
  - Club 100 photograph album and notebook, 1989-2001 (Box 1,839, Folder 1-3)
    This box contains one 1997 Distinguished Artist Awards Show Betacam.
  - Performing Arts Council and Music Center Unified Fund Annual Reports, 1966-2002 (Box 1,840, Folder 1-5)
  - Music Center Unified Fund and Music Center Arts and Education Fund campaign files, 1968-2001 (Box 1,841, Folder 1-18)
  - Music Center Unified Fund campaign files and donor photographs, 1975-1999 (Box 1,842, Folder 1-11)
    Ths box contains two VHSs and include the following: Fulfillment Fund Candy and Aaron Spelling Tribute and Tribute to Andrew Lloyd Webber at Regent Beverly Wilshire Hotel.
  - Music Center Unified Fund Annual Reports and samples book, 1971-1988 (Box 1,843, Folder 1-7)
  - Music Center Unified Fund and Mercado files, 1981-1997 (Box 1,844, Folder 1-38)
    This box contains one KNX Music Center Unified Fund audiocassette.
  - Music Center Unified Fund binders and ephemera, 1995-1997 (Box 1,845, Folder 1-7)
  - Music Center Unified Fund and Mercado memorabilia, circa 1979-1981 (Box 1,846, Folder 1-4)
  - Music Center Unified Fund and Mercado press files, 1982-1998 (Box 1,847, Folder 1-16)
  - Music Center Fundraising book paste-ups, 1976-1978 (Box 1,848, Folder 1-5)
  - Music Center Unified Fund Score and Runaway Bride binders, 1999-2001 (Box 1,849, Folder 1-3)
  - Fraternity of Friends photograph albums and newsletters, 1979-2008 (Box 1,850, Folder 1-11)
  - Fraternity of Friends invitations, 1980-2005 (Box 1,851, Folder 1-4)
  - Fraternity of Friends rosters and invitations, 1995-2004 (Box 1,852, Folder 1-7)
  - Fraternity of Friends invitations, 1997-2008 (Box 1,853, Folder 1-5)
    This box contains one The Writer, The Singer, The Song VHS and one Fraternity at Rand DVD.
  - Fraternity of Friends scrapbook, 1977-1979 (Box 1,854, Folder 1)
  - Entertainment Council and LA Alive! files, 1985-1990 (Box 1,855, Folder 1-25)
  - LA Alive! Galas, photographs, and Dorothy B. Chandler Awards files, 1980-2000 (Box 1,856, Folder 1-17)
  - LA Alive! programs, photographs, and publicity, 1990-2002 (Box 1,857, Folder 1-7)
  - LA Alive! programs and publicity, 2002-2008 (Box 1,858, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains one CD dated 2002.
  - LA Alive! programs, photographs, and slides, 1989-2011 (Box 1,859, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains one CD dated 2008.
  - LA Alive! digital and audiovisual materials, 1989-2008 (Box 1,860, Folder 1-12)
    This box contains ten VHSs, one CD, and one DVD.
  - Family Festival photographs, 2001-2002 (Box 1,861, Folder 1-3)
  - A Community of Angels project files, 2001-2002 (Box 1,862, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains one Angel of Music VHS and three Angel of Music CDs.
- Series 9: Music Center Education Division files, 1970-2014
  The Music Center Education Division (MCED) was founded in 1979 to support a positive and dynamic future for the Music Center by engaging people with the arts -- at the Center, in schools and in communities -- and to provide leadership to advance the quality and scope of arts education in Southern California. The Education Division is committed to the belief that experiencing the arts enhances the quality of life for all people, and is a crucial part of the development of every child. Each year MCED presents performances and other arts programs in hundreds of public and private schools with a full spectrum of arts experiences to nurture the creative potential in students and teachers and to develop future artists, informed audiences, and dedicated arts supporters. The Division's varied programs offer a distinguished roster of artists representing diverse cultures, disciplines, and styles.
  Source: Music Center Performing Arts Center of Los Angeles County press kit, Music Center Education Division, Box 1,964, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
  The Music Center Education Division (MCED) files range in date from 1970-2014 and contain press files; programs; brochures; flyers; binders; newsletters; textbooks; proposals; resolutions; certificates; study guides; digital materials; audiovisual materials; Winterfest files; Spotlight files, photographs, and certificates; Bravo Awards files; Very Special Arts Festival programs, brochures, clippings, photograph albums, and audiovisual materials; pARTy photograph albums and audiovisual materials; ReachOut files and Shining Stars photographs.
  - Music Center Education Division and Community Access Program press files, 1979-1996 (Box 1863, Folder 1-13)
  - Music Center Education Division programs and brochures, 1981-2008 (Box 1864, Folder 1-5)
    This box contains one 2008 Teaching Artist Training DVD.
  - Music Center Education Division flyers and brochures, 1982-1987 (Box 1865, Folder 1-4)
  - Music Center Education Division programs and brochures, 1985-2009 (Box 1866, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains one LA 36 CD.
  - Music Center Education Division binders, 1994-1995, 2000 (Box 1867, Folder 1-7)
  - Music Center Education Division programs and newsletters, 1984-2009 (Box 1868, Folder 1-12)
  - Music Center Education Division programs, 1981-2014 (Box 1869, Folder 1-15)
  - Music Center Education Division binders, 1988-2004 (Box 1870, Folder 1-5)
  - Exploring Art, Introducing Art, and Art Connections Level 5 textbooks, 1998-1999 (Box 1871, Folder 1-5)
  - Teacher Art Connections Level K-2, 1998 (Box 1872, Folder 1-3)
  - Teacher Art Connections Level 3-5, 1998 (Box 1873, Folder 1-3)
  - Music Center Arts and Education Fund proposal to General Motors, 1970 (Box 1874, Folder 1-2)
    This box also contains a Founding Director Joan Boyett retirement gathering oversize color photograph dated 2001.
  - Music Center Education Division resolutions and certificates, 1970-2006 (Box 1875, Folder 1-3)
  - Artsource Resource Packages Level K-3, 1995 (Box 1876, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains four audiocassettes and four VHSs.
  - Artsource Resource Packages Level 4-5, 1995 (Box 1877, Folder 1-3)
    This box contains three audiocassettes and three VHSs.
  - Artsource study guides and Art Connections Level K-1, 1995-1999 (Box 1878, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains two audiocassettes and two VHSs.
  - Art Works, Understanding Art, and Art in Focus textbooks, 1997-2000 (Box 1879, Folder 1-5)
    This box contains one Art Works! VHS.
  - Artsource Performing Arts Packages 2-3 and Art Connections Level 2-3, 1998-1999 (Box 1880, Folder 1-4)
  - Artsource Institute for Educators study guides and Art Connections Level 4, undated (Box 1881, Folder 1-3)
  - Artsource Institute for Educators study guides and Art Connections Level 4, 2003 (Box 1882, Folder 1)
    This box contains one audiocassette and one VHS.
  - Music Center Education Division digital and audiovisual materials, 1989-2004 (Box 1883, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains eight VHSs and five CDs which includes the following: Artists in Residence, youth programs, The Hating Pot, Jamal Story interview, and Writer, Singer, Song.
  - Music Center Education Division digital and audiovisual materials, 1990-2007 (Box 1884, Folder 1-19)
    This box contains five VHSs, two Betacams, six DVDs, five CDs, and one 1 inch videotape and includes the following productions: World City, Performing Books, Pillow Theater, A Place To Call Home, and To Dream.